<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Postgraduate on Harp Seal Pup Nursery and Caring Center</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/tags/postgraduate/</link><description>Recent content in Postgraduate on Harp Seal Pup Nursery and Caring Center</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/tags/postgraduate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 'Close' and the 'Far' of the Internet</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/postgraduate-the-close-and-the-far-of-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:07:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/postgraduate-the-close-and-the-far-of-the-internet/</guid><description>The drawing titled &amp;ldquo;The &amp;lsquo;close&amp;rsquo; and the &amp;lsquo;far&amp;rsquo; of the Internet&amp;rdquo; depicts a spider-web-like structure with numerous cells, each containing an individual seated in front of a computer. This visual metaphor encapsulates the interconnected nature of the internet, illustrating how people occupy distinct positions within a vast network.
The spider-web structure symbolizes the internet, where each individual is connected through technology, allowing for the exchange of messages and information. Despite physical distances, individuals on the internet can feel an artificial sense of closeness, as if they are in proximity, when in reality, they might be geographically distant.</description></item><item><title>Opinions and Suggestions on Restricting Plastic Bag Usage</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/postgraduate-opinions-and-suggestions-on-restricting-plastic-bag-usage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:50:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/postgraduate-opinions-and-suggestions-on-restricting-plastic-bag-usage/</guid><description>Dear Editors,
I am writing to express my concerns about the unsuccessful restrictions on plastic bag usage in some regions, as reported in your recent article on &amp;ldquo;white pollution&amp;rdquo;. While I firmly support the ban on plastic bags, it is crucial to understand why they remain widely used and address the root causes.
Plastic bags are popular due to their affordability, lightweight nature, and convenience – advantages that other alternatives often lack.</description></item></channel></rss>