<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rfc on Harp Seal Pup Nursery and Caring Center</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/tags/rfc/</link><description>Recent content in Rfc on Harp Seal Pup Nursery and Caring Center</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 07:51:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/tags/rfc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RFC 2428: FTP Extensions for IPv6 and NATs IPv6和NAT的FTP扩展</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc2428/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:05:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc2428/</guid><description>Network Working Group
M. Allman, NASA Lewis/Sterling Software
S. Ostermann, Ohio University
C. Metz, The Inner Net
Request for Comments: 2428
Category: Standards Track
September 1998
Status of this Memo 本备忘录的状态 This document specifies an Internet standards track protocol for the Internet community, and requests discussion and suggestions for improvements. Please refer to the current edition of the &amp;ldquo;Internet Official Protocol Standards&amp;rdquo; (STD 1) for the standardization state and status of this protocol.</description></item><item><title>RFC 1579: Firewall-Friendly FTP 防火墙友好型FTP</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc1579/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:49:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc1579/</guid><description>Network Working Group
S. Bellovin
AT&amp;amp;T Bell Laboratories
Request for Comments: 1579
Category: Informational
February 1994
Status of this Memo 本备忘录的状态 This document provides information for the Internet community. This document does not specify an Internet standard of any kind. Distribution of this document is unlimited.
本文档为互联网社区提供信息。本文档并未规定任何类型的互联网标准。本文档的分发不受限制。
Abstract 摘要 This memo describes a suggested change to the behavior of FTP client programs. No protocol modifications are required, though we outline some that might be useful.</description></item><item><title>RFC 3659: Extensions to FTP FTP的扩展</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc3659/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 23:05:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc3659/</guid><description>Network Working Group
P. Hethmon
Hethmon Software
Request for Comments: 3659
Updates: 959
March 2007
Status of This Memo 本备忘录的状态 This document specifies an Internet standards track protocol for the Internet community, and requests discussion and suggestions for improvements. Please refer to the current edition of the &amp;ldquo;Internet Official Protocol Standards&amp;rdquo; (STD 1) for the standardization state and status of this protocol. Distribution of this memo is unlimited.
本文档规定了互联网社区的一个互联网标准轨道协议，并请求讨论和改进建议。请参阅“互联网官方协议标准”（STD 1）的当前版本，了解本协议的标准化状态和状态。本备忘录的分发是不受限制的。</description></item><item><title>RFC 959: File Transfer Protocol 文件传输协议 (FTP)</title><link>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:37:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://tategotoazarasi.github.io/post/rfc959/</guid><description>Network Working Group
Request for Comments: 959
J. Postel
J. Reynolds
ISI
October 1985
Status of this Memo 本备忘录的状态 This memo is the official specification of the File Transfer Protocol (FTP). Distribution of this memo is unlimited.
本备忘录是文件传输协议（FTP）的官方规范。本备忘录的分发不受限制。
The following new optional commands are included in this edition of the specification:
在这版规范中包括了以下新的可选命令：
CDUP (Change to Parent Directory 切换到父目录) SMNT (Structure Mount 结构挂载) STOU (Store Unique 存储唯一文件) RMD (Remove Directory 移除目录) MKD (Make Directory 创建目录) PWD (Print Directory 打印目录) SYST (System 系统).</description></item></channel></rss>